lastlemon.com 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Last Lemon

We take privacy extremely seriously. Our Privacy Policy below describes what we do with data we collect.

## We DO store

Submitted email addressee and IP address of submittor.

Like most websites, lastlemon.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the type that browsers typically make available, such as language preference, browser type and time-stamp (i.e. the date and time of each visit). We do this so we can better understand user trends.

lastlemon.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information, the Internet Protocol (IP) address.

lastlemon.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of text that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.  
lastlemon.com uses cookies to identify and track visitors and their usage of lastlemon.com.

lastlemon.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using lastlemon.com.

## Protection of Information

lastlemon.com discloses potentially personally-identifying information only to those of its employees and software contractors that:

(a) Need to know that information in order to process it on lastlemon.com’s behalf or to provide services available on lastlemon.com website, and (b) That have agreed not to disclose it to anyone else. Some of those employees or software contractors may be located outside of your home country; by using lastlemon.com you consent to the transfer of such information to them. lastlemon.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees and contractors, lastlemon.com discloses potentially personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when lastlemon.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the IP or rights of lastlemon.com, third parties or the public at large.

## Amendments to our Privacy Policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, lastlemon.com may occasionally amend its Privacy Policy, and at our discretion. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any Privacy Policy amendments. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Terms of Service for our Happy/Sad/Love & Friendship projects can be found [here](http://lastlemon.com/terms-of-service/).
